{
    "id": "1cca8a0dd1404dceb05c7c5900d4c729",
    "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Where …………………. you ..................... now?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is, go",
                "are, going",
                "have been, going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9e1e2ec39a14fce995cdce0ba9fee39"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... . Don’t disturb him now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is studying",
                "are studying",
                "has been studying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79809a62ca334656b66c2c3e546dcc42"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ...................... on my feet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand",
                "am standing",
                "are standing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1698586c3aa44ac5960a2a5f945273b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani ..................... the plants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is watering",
                "am watering",
                "are watering"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "985ed1a950754c1d8c62807d28187dee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................… to hear from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "am waiting",
                "are waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94964c7a07dd455f9745b69528379166"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... for the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is preparing",
                "are preparing",
                "was preparing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c54a6bc74404f298c3f2c162ecf9d06"
        },
        {
            "question": "Radha ...................... a sweater for her daughter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am knitting",
                "is knitting",
                "am knitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36dc2086d389442ab7db91e1e2204f4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul ………………….. his homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is doing",
                "are doing",
                "am doing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf606343f7dc45c7bb6d533c293a8acf"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "are waiting",
                "am waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e02cdcdfe85441f8d837c77bc2d2765"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ..................... the cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is chasing",
                "are chasing",
                "am chasing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efc415e0debe4c4caaf80419eba342f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother ..................... a cake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is baking",
                "are baking",
                "am baking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc487646c9a545f48dc5ea14d1a8e926"
        },
        {
            "question": "Father ..................... his bike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is fixing",
                "am fixing",
                "are fixing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddae3fcdd0e247ac8453416ff432ee07"
        }
    ]
}